<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>Services </title>
    <description>Services  Feed</description>
    <link></link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    <atom:link href="/service/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title>Realtime Visuals</title>
            
            <media:content url="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65d910b67416578214544695_render.png" medium="image"/>
            
            <link>/service/realtime-visuals/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>/service/realtime-visuals/</guid>
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The tech&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using custom software tools, we&#39;re able to take anything that sends data out, and create&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What we offer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
            
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Projection Mapping</title>
            
            <media:content url="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb2803_Project%204-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
            
            <link>/service/projection-mapping/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>/service/projection-mapping/</guid>
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The tech&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What we offer&lt;/h3&gt;
</content>
            
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Light Shows</title>
            
            <media:content url="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65ea0a25c4c642466b64cf09_lights-render-min.png" medium="image"/>
            
            <link>/service/light-show/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>/service/light-show/</guid>
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The tech&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Events are where the magic of connections happen. But so many of us stick to the mundane walls of static decor and string lights in mason jars.&lt;br&gt;
What if your musician had a 30ft curtain of lights behind them, synced to the rhythm of their music? And what if you could feel euphoria by being surrounded by 4ft light bars?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, we can do both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We guarantee that our pocket-friendly lighting solutions can kick the mundane out of any party. As long as the mundane is not a person- we don’t really have the power to do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65dfb38775be7428c023e760_image%20(1).png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using our 10ft to 30ft light curtains or 8 controllable light bars, we can add a sense of wonder to any party. Our tech can display countless different animations and can even sync with the music on play.&lt;br&gt;
We recommend the curtains for a more immersive experience, and the light bars can be customised based on the tone of your event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
            
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Interactive Instillations</title>
            
            <media:content url="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65ea09b31e97ad6aa6de2362_render-min.png" medium="image"/>
            
            <link>/service/interactive-instillations/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>/service/interactive-instillations/</guid>
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The tech&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use 3D cameras to track movement, gestures and depth. All of which can be fed into a wall projection, LED curtain or any of our other visual experiences. Essentially , we elevate any event by activating the art on display.&lt;br&gt;
We are currently working on creating ready to use interactive set pieces for any space of your choice. Reach out to us if you are curious about what else is possible, or if you have questions about pricing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
            
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Augmented Reality</title>
            
            <media:content url="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/65cd4810adae93d8cfeb26e4/65ea247dd8a19d889e27c1e7_AR-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
            
            <link>/service/augmented-reality/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>/service/augmented-reality/</guid>
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The tech&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine if you could have information materialise before your eyes in real time. While that may be possible through other nefarious means, WebAR is the next best (legal) tool to make that happen.&lt;br&gt;
‍&lt;br&gt;
A poster can animate in front of your eyes, or your clients can explore a 3D model of your product. We can use image tracking to fix an animation, or even make custom face tracking filters. We can even create an AR version of pets that you can travel with! The best part is, we don’t use an app or downloadable content to make this happen for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What we offer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team at {Name} is working diligently at making creative, ready to use templates at pocket-friendly prices. We currently have one out of the box option that transforms your boring advertisement or poster into a full fledged video.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
            
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
